// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Pre-revolutionary French society was divided into three ______.",
    answer: "estates",
    options: [
      "tithes",
      "communes",
      "estates",
      "guillotines"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "When did King Louis XVII ascended to the throne of France?",
    answer: "1774",
    options: [
      "1698",
      "1789",
      "1774",
      "1614"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who wrote the book The Social Contarct",
    answer: "Rousseau",
    options: [
      "John Locke",
      "Rousseau",
      "Montesquieu",
      "Marie Antoinette"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Marie Antoinette was a _______ princess.",
    answer: "Austrian",
    options: [
      "American",
      "France",
      "Austrian",
      "none of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the extreme sitauation when the basic means of livelihood are endangered.",
    answer: "Subsistence crisis",
    options: [
      "Subsistence crisis",
      "Economic crisis",
      "both (a) and (b)",
      "none of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A triangular slave trade took place between Europe,the America and",
    answer: "Africa",
    options: [
      "Asia",
      "Australia",
      "Africa",
      "none of these",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Upon becoming free the slave wore",
    answer: "red cap",
    options: [
      "green cap",
      "red cap",
      "yellow cap",
      "blue cap",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who were not considerd 'passive citizens'?",
    answer: "wealthy people",
    options: [
      "Women",
      "children",
      "Non-propertied man",
      "wealthy people",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "When was Robiespierre guillotined",
    answer: "1794",
    options: [
      "1789",
      "1614",
      "1794",
      "1797",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "When was Napoleon bonarpate defeated at the battle of Waterloo",
    answer: "1815",
    options: [
      "1815",
      "1777",
      "1616",
      "none of these",
    ]
  },
];